partycity.ca 2017-12-28

# Privacy Policy - Party City Canada

Privacy and Security

Last updated: May 2017.

Party City takes the privacy of our customers very seriously. We understand that you want to know how information about you is used, stored, and shared and we know the importance of protecting your personal information. Nobody wants to have his or her personal information sold or misused. We do not rent or sell your personal information to anyone, period. 

This privacy policy (“Privacy Policy”) applies to customer information collected and used by Party City and its affiliates (together, “Party City”). This Privacy Policy does not cover any information collected by third-party sites or content or applications that may link to, or be accessible from or on, our website. We collect information about you from a variety of sources, including the information we collect from you in person, the information we collect from you when you visit our website [www.partycity.com](http://www.partycity.com/) or its related subdomains (“Website”), and the information that we collect about you from other sources. By visiting and using the Website, you are accepting the terms described in this Privacy Policy. 

Please take a moment to familiarize yourself with our privacy practices and let us know if you have any questions. 

Types of Information We Collect

We collect information to deliver the products and services you request and to help improve your Party City experience. Some information that we collect form you can be used to identify you or can be reasonably used in connection with other information to identify you. This information is called “personal information” and includes your name, postal address, email address, phone number, and payment information. 

You share personal information with us when you make an in-store or online purchase with us, when you create an account on one of our Websites or mobile services, when you visit or post a comment on one of our social media pages, and when you contact us or request customer service. 

Other types of information that we collect cannot be used to personally identify you, but provides Party City with information that we use to improve the products and services we offer to you. This information includes details about your internet connection, traffic data, IP address, and the equipment you use to access our Website and usage details. It may be collected by Party City or it may be collected through third party advertisers or partners who provide the advertisements on our Website. This information is collected automatically through the use of cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies. Information that is collected through the use of third party cookies, web beacons, and other third party tracking technologies are subject to such third parties' privacy policies and opt-out mechanisms and are not governed by this Policy. 

In order to invite others to view your Party City page or to use Party City's online invitation services, you must provide us with email addresses of your guests or invitees. In order to send messages to your guests or invitees, we require that you submit to Party City current, valid email addresses for your guests or invitees. When you send messages to your guests or invitees, we collect and retain the email addresses or other pertinent contact information for those persons to whom you send the message. 

How We Use Your Information

Party City uses the personal information that we collect about you or that you provide to us: to process and ship your online orders ;for marketing or advertising purposes; to inform you about promotional offers; to maintain your user account; to keep track of your order history; to respond to customer support inquiries; to present our Website and its contents to you; to tell you about changes to our Website; to let you know about products or services; to allow you to participate in interactive features on our Website in a way that we describe to you at the time that you provide Party City your personal information; to fulfill any other purpose for which you provide it. 

The non-personal information that we collect may automatically be combined with other information that you provide and may be aggregated and used for statistical purposes. It helps us to improve our Website and to deliver better and more personalized products, services and advertisements. It also helps us to estimate how many people may be interested in certain products, store your user preferences allowing us to customize the Website to your individual interests, recognize you when you revisit our Website, and speed up your online experience with Party City. 

For its online invitation services or other services that Party City makes available from time to time where you provide us email addresses or other contact information of your guests and invitees, Party City may retain such email addresses and contact information that you provide to us, but we will not use these email addresses and contact information to send promotional communications, newsletters, or services announcements without your express permission. Additionally, we will not intentionally sell or otherwise disclose to any unaffiliated third party the email addresses or other contact information of your guests and invitees that you submit to us. 

Information Sharing

Party City does not rent or sell your personal information to third parties. However, we may disclose the personal information that we collect or that you provide to us as described in this Privacy Policy to our subsidiaries and affiliates or to carefully selected third parties that we use to support our business and bring products to you, such as our service providers, partners and suppliers. 

We may use the services of third parties to collect and use anonymous information about your visits and interactions with our Website through the use of technologies such as cookies to personalize advertisements for goods and services. To learn more, or to opt-out of receiving online display advertisements tailored to your interests by our third party partners, visit the Network Advertising Initiative at [www.networkadvertising.org/choices](http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices). 

Your personal information may also be disclosed to enforce our terms of use, to comply with any court order, law or legal process, or government or regulatory request, or if we believe that disclosure is necessary or appropriate to protect the rights, property, or safety of Party City, our customers or others. 

Accessing Your Information

At any time, you can review and change your personal information by logging into the Website and visiting your account profile page. Here, you can make changes to your name, password, postal address, email address, phone number, or credit card information that you had previously entered. 

Information Security

We have implemented measures designed to secure your personal information from accidental loss and from unauthorized access, use, alteration and disclosure. Party City stores and processes your personal information on its computers and servers in the United States. We protect your personal information by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards in compliance with applicable U.S. federal and state regulations. All personal information that you may provide on any of Websites will be Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encrypted. Party City also uses computer safeguards such as firewalls and data encryption methods to protect your information. 

The safety and security of your information also depends on you. For instance, you can start by using a complex and well-chosen password. You should avoid sharing your password or using any information that others can easily learn about you, such as a family member's name or birthday. We also recommend that you frequently change your password. You can also install and regularly update antivirus and firewall software to protect your computer or device from external attacks by malicious users. When you are finished with a session on our Website, be sure that you log out and close the browser window so nobody can pick up where you left off. 

Unfortunately, no method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure. Therefore, we cannot guarantee the absolute security of your information. Any transmission of personal information is at your own risk and Party City is not responsible for the circumvention of any privacy settings or security measures contained on the Website. 

Cookies and Other Tracking Technology

Cookies are small data files that most websites store, access and maintain on the hard drive of your computer. We may use technologies, such as our own cookies, to provide you with personalized online display advertising tailored to your interests. To opt out of our cookies used for this particular online advertising, [click here](http://dtmc.partycity.com/adinfo/choice/prod/?type=fpc&cid=2334&cname=Party%20City&cmagic=7e3b7a&clogo=2334.png&loc=us&lang=en-us). 

You may refuse to accept browser cookies by activating the appropriate setting on your browser. However, if you select this setting you may be unable to access certain parts of our Website. Unless you have adjusted your browser setting so that it will refuse cookies, our system will issue cookies when you visit our Website. 

Certain features of our Website may use local stored objects (Flash cookies) to collect and store information about your preferences and navigation to, from and on our Website. These data files may be created on your computer when you visit our Website. Flash cookies are most often used to enhance your experience on our Website, for example, by allowing the look of a website you frequently visit to appear personalized. Flash cookies will not access or remember your e-mail address or other personal information unless you willingly provide such information. 

Our Website may also contain small electronic files known as web beacons (also referred to as clear gifs. pixel tags and single-pixel gifs) that permit Party City, for example, to count users who have visited particular webpages or and can be used for other related website statistics, such as verifying our system and server integrity. 

“Do Not Track”

We do not support Do Not Track (“DNT”). Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser. 

Third Party Links

Our Website may contain links to other websites that are not operated by us. If you click on a third party link, you will be directed to that third party's site. We recommend that you review the Privacy Policy of each site you visit. Party City does not control, and assumes no responsibility for the content, privacy policies or practices of any third party sites or services. 

Communications

We may use your personal information to contact you with newsletters, marketing or promotional materials and other information that may be of interest to you. You may opt out of receiving any, or all, of these communications from us by following the unsubscribe link or instructions provided in any email we send. 

California Residents

Party City values your privacy and we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. Under California law, California residents are entitled to ask us for a notice describing what categories of personal information we share with third parties for their direct marketing purposes. The notice will identify the categories of personal information shared with third parties, as well as the name and address of the third parties that receive such personal information. You can process that request free of charge by sending an email to the address below. 

Children's Online Privacy

This Website is not marketed to, and does not knowingly collect or maintain personal information from, children under the age of 13. If we learn that we have collected or received personal information from a child under the age of 13 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. If you believe we might have any information from or about a child under the age of 13, please let us know. 

Business Transaction

If Party City is involved in a merger, acquisition, asset sale, bankruptcy or reorganization, your personal information may be shared, as well as retained by us. By providing us with your personal information, you consent to that transfer. 

Opt-Out

If you wish to opt-out of receiving online communications from Party City, our partners, or our third party providers, you can choose the unsubscribe or opt-out link contained in the email and you will no longer receive communications. 

Changes to This Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy is subject to change at the sole discretion of Party City, and the updated Privacy Policy will be posted on our Website. This Privacy Policy was last updated as of the date provided above. Continued use of the Website after Party City posts a revised Privacy Policy signifies your acceptance of the revised Privacy Policy. Please check back frequently and review the Privacy Policy for any updated terms or changes. 

Contact Us

If you have any questions or comments regarding this Privacy Policy, please do not hesitate to contact us at [privacyquestions@partycity.com](mailto:privacyquestions@partycity.com). 

You may also contact our corporate headquarters by writing to us at: 

Party City Corporation  
Suite 1  
25 Green Pond Road  
Rockaway, NJ 07866
